AFARAIT SULAIMON BOLA

Address: 14, Alhaji Razak Street, Email: afaraitsulaimon@gmail.com

Off Benson Akinyele Str, Telephone: 08032716181

Oke-Afa, Jakande, Ejigbo, Lagos State. GitHub: https://github.com/afaraitsulaimon

Career Goal:

To showcase my talent and expertise as a Software Developer/Product Manager and help in organizational development utilizing my knowledge in Software Development & Product Management. Dedicated to embracing and learning new technologies, while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

Technical Skills:

Knowledge of web application development using:

- PHP, Laravel
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, ReactJs
- Python/Django

Proficient in Development IDEs including: •

Visual Studio

Proficient in communication tools including:

• Slack

Proficient in utilize version control tools: •

• Git

Adept in database administration: •

MYSQL server

Outstanding abilities to:

• Critical thinking in product development

Other Skills:

- Ability in development of new and existing product to MVP level using product management skills.
- Ability to use Figma tools in building Wireframes and Prototypes.
- Ability to use Jira.
- Ability to use Miro.
- Ability to work with Scrum Framework.

Projects:

- Single Personal Page (Built using Html, CSS and Bootstrap).
 afaraitsulaimon.github.io/sbafarait/
- Tricycle Design (Built using Html and CSS).
 afaraitsulaimon.github.io/tricycle-design/
- Simple Archive for achieve user (Built using Html, CSS, Bootstrap, Jquery and PHP). afaraitsulaimon.github.io/myarchive/
- A story Web Application (Built using Html, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript and PHP). https://github.com/afaraitsulaimon/mystoryhour (www.nastory.tk)

Work Experience:

Enifeni Organization

Software Developer/Product Manager - March 2021 till date

Duties:

- Training of the apprentice in the company
- Building MVP (Minimum Viable Products)
- ❖ Zenith Bank PLC, Matori Branch, Ladipo Road, Mushin, Lagos

Marketer - Jan 2014 – June 2019

Duties:

- Acquire more customers for the bank, both personal and business customers.
- Help customers in acquisition of loan.
- Following up with existing and new customers to help retain them in the company.
- ❖ Jumia.com.ng, 6b, Universal Close off Surulere Road, Adeniyi Jones, Ikeja.
 Online Sales Consultant (J-Force Team) Feb. 2013 August 2013

Duties:

- To help customers that are willing to order online to order their items.
- To advertise the services of Jumia more both online and one on one to people Achievement
- Made the company make more sales and go at a wider range in making sales
- NYSC (National Youth Service Corps) Government Technical Science College, Mada Station. Nasarawa State. (March 2010-Feb 2011).

Duties:

Teaching Electronics

Educational Profile:

- Higher National Diploma in Physics Electronics, Lagos State polytechnic, Ikorodu, Lagos state - 2008
- National Diploma in Electrical Electronics Engineering, Moshood Abiola polytechnic, Ogun State - 2004

- Senior Secondary School certificate Suzan Martins Comprehensive, High School, Akinbayode Street, Papa Ajao, Mushin, Lagos state 2002
- Senior Secondary School Certificate, Saint Joseph Boy's Secondary School Surulere, Lagos State. - 2001

TRAINING:

- Website Design and Web Development Alabian Solutions, 22 Olu Akerele street off Lagoon Hospital, Balogun bus-stop, off Allen Avenue, Ikeja, Lagos July to September 2018.
- Product Management at Utiva Training School Online Training April 2021 May 2021.

REFEREES:

On Request.